或者我们可以做一些其他的事情，我们可以做最大和最小，以及交集和并集。
Or we can do some other things, we can do max and min, and intersection and union.
我想为幺半群提供一个反例
I wanna provide a counter example to monoids and
表明我们不能将半群提升为具有身份的幺半群。
show that we can't promote a semi group to a monoid with an identity.
所以一个例子是兴趣部分。
So one example of that would be interest section.
因此，如果我进行交集并尝试进行交集，让我们将我的小模板复制到此处。
So if I make intersection and I try to, let's just copy my little template here.
我试着说好吧，我有这个和那个的交集，
And I try to say okay, well, I have the intersection of this and that one,
我们将使用像低破折号交叉点，对，这个和另一个。
we'll use like low dash intersection, right, of this and the other one.
现在我将如何提供价值
And now how would I provide a value
也就是说，一个起始值来获得列表的交集，对吗？
that said, a starting value to get the intersection of the list, right?
如果我连接了那个，如果我有这个列表的交集，并且
If I concated that, if I had an intersection of this list, and
我想将它与另一个列表的交集连接起来。
I wanted to concat that with the intersection of another list.
呸呸呸呸呸呸。
Blah, blah, blah, blah, blah.
如果我提供一个空列表会发生什么，
What would happen is if I provided an empty list,
没有任何东西会与它相交。
nothing would ever intersect with it.
我总是会得到一个空列表。
I would always get an empty list back.
如果我提供了所有可能的东西的列表，那可能会奏效。
If I provided a list of every possible anything, that might work.
[笑] 但我不知道该怎么做。
[LAUGH] But I don't know how to do that.
所以我们只想说这个路口没有空的。
So we're just gonna say that intersection does not have an empty.
因此它只是一个半群，它不是一个幺半群。
Therefore it is only a semigroup, it is not a monoid.
有趣的是，这是一个联合，我们可以给它一个空列表，然后
And so that's interestingly a union, we could just give it an empty list and
那将是身份。
that'll be identity.
所以，联合是幺半群，交集不是。
So, union is a monoid, intersection is not.